HANGYABOLY is a "freemouse" experimental cartoonish font, I drew the letters directly and spontaneously into the font software with the mouse (thats what I call "freemouse", after "freehand"). No scratch, no background tracing. It means Ant Hill, I named it after the "g" what reminded me an ant.

This font is free for PERSONAL use only. For any commercial use (anything you make money from), you must send a paypal donation to myhandwritings@gmail.com.

This is almost a full version, with Central and Western European accents and letters, plus Cyrillic!

Feel free to contact me via myhandwritings@gmail.com
also about the following:
- If it does not cover the language extension you specially needed (some are missing though)
- Discovering kerning problems while using 
- Or any other question or feedback. 

You MAY NOT sell my fonts or claim them as your own.
You MAY NOT edit or rename my fonts.

You MAY redistribute my fonts if:
1. You credit me (Roland Huse).
2. Keep the READ ME file intact within the zip folder.
3. Provide a link back to my website (www.rolandhuse.com).

Thank you & I hope you like this font,

Roland
http://www.rolandhuse.com
https://www.facebook.com/pages/Runes-And-Fonts/123221817784772
